Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024 Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024 Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024

Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024 Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024 Black Friday SALE 50% OFF on the Qi product line & all QODE plugins Discount code: BLACKFRIDAY2024

[0](javascript:void(0))

[](javascript:void(0))

[0](javascript:void(0))

* ###### Qode ThemeForest Themes
    
    * [Creative](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/creative-wordpress-themes/)452
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/creative-wordpress-themes/)452
        * [Agency](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/agency-wordpress-themes/)135
        * [Portfolio](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/portfolio-wordpress-themes/)130
        * [Multipurpose](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/multipurpose-wordpress-themes/)104
        * [Photography](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/photography-wordpress-themes/)48
        * [Architecture](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/architecture-wordpress-themes/)35
    * [Business](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/business-wordpress-themes/)192
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/business-wordpress-themes/)192
        * [Corporate](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/corporate-wordpress-themes/)61
        * [Services & Industry](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/services-industry-wordpress-themes/)49
        * [Nonprofit](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/nonprofit-wordpress-themes/)28
        * [Medical](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/medical-wordpress-themes/)28
        * [Marketing](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/marketing-wordpress-themes/)14
        * [Law](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/law-wordpress-themes/)13
    * [Online Store](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/online-store-wordpress-themes/)187
    * [Wellness & Lifestyle](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/wellness-lifestyle-wordpress-themes/)111
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/wellness-lifestyle-wordpress-themes/)111
        * [Sport & Fitness](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/sport-fitness-wordpress-themes/)51
        * [Wellness](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/wellness-wordpress-themes/)19
        * [Beauty](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/beauty-wordpress-themes/)19
        * [Fashion](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/fashion-wordpress-themes/)15
        * [Lifestyle](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/lifestyle-wordpress-themes/)7
    * [Food & Restaurants](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/food-restaurants-wordpress-themes/)108
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/food-restaurants-wordpress-themes/)108
        * [Restaurant](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/restaurant-wordpress-themes/)53
        * [Café & Bakery](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/cafe-bakery-wordpress-themes/)29
        * [Food](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/food-wordpress-themes/)16
        * [Pub & Bar](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/pub-bar-wordpress-themes/)10
    * [Blog & Magazine](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/blog-magazine-wordpress-themes/)86
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/blog-magazine-wordpress-themes/)86
        * [Personal Blog](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/personal-blog-wordpress-themes/)55
        * [Magazine](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/magazine-wordpress-themes/)31
    * [Entertainment](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/entertainment-wordpress-themes/)76
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/entertainment-wordpress-themes/)76
        * [Music](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/music-wordpress-themes/)29
        * [Events](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/events-wordpress-themes/)20
        * [Film & Theater](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/film-theater-wordpress-themes/)17
        * [Gaming](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/gaming-wordpress-themes/)10
    * [Technology](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/technology-wordpress-themes/)63
    * [Travel](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/travel-wordpress-themes/)32
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/travel-wordpress-themes/)32
        * [Travel Agency](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/travel-agency-wordpress-themes/)18
        * [Hotel](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/hotel-wordpress-themes/)14
    * [Education](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/education-wordpress-themes/)25
        * [All](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/education-wordpress-themes/)25
        * [Online Learning](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/online-learning-wordpress-themes/)15
        * [Kids](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/kids-wordpress-themes/)10
    * [Wedding](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/wedding-wordpress-themes/)20
    * [Real Estate](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/real-estate-wordpress-themes/)14
    * [Listing](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-category/listing-wordpress-themes/)11
        * [White](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/white-wordpress-themes/)614
        * [Grey](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/grey-wordpress-themes/)696
        * [Black](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/black-wordpress-themes/)455
        * [Brown](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/brown-wordpress-themes/)261
        * [Beige](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/beige-wordpress-themes/)490
        * [Yellow](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/yellow-wordpress-themes/)190
        * [Orange](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/orange-wordpress-themes/)182
        * [Red](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/red-wordpress-themes/)176
        * [Pink](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/pink-wordpress-themes/)210
        * [Purple](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/purple-wordpress-themes/)137
        * [Blue](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/blue-wordpress-themes/)334
        * [Turquoise](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/turquoise-wordpress-themes/)171
        * [Green](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/green-wordpress-themes/)272
        * [Multicolor](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-color/multi-wordpress-themes/)291
        * [Modern](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/modern-wordpress-themes/)873
        * [Creative](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/creative-wordpress-themes/)431
        * [Clean](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/clean-wordpress-themes/)354
        * [Colorful](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/colorful-wordpress-themes/)335
        * [Elegant](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/elegant-wordpress-themes/)332
        * [Bold](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/bold-wordpress-themes/)282
        * [Pastel](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/pastel-wordpress-themes/)301
        * [Urban](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/urban-wordpress-themes/)271
        * [Feminine](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/feminine-wordpress-themes/)226
        * [Minimal](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/minimal-wordpress-themes/)204
        * [Digital](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/digital-wordpress-themes/)187
        * [Vintage](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/vintage-wordpress-themes/)150
        * [Alternative](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/alternative-wordpress-themes/)148
        * [Luxurious](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-style/luxurious-wordpress-themes/)133
        * [Scroll Animations](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/scroll-animations-wordpress-themes/)246
        * [Typography Effects](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/typography-effects-wordpress-themes/)219
        * [Parallax Effects](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/parallax-effects-wordpress-themes/)169
        * [Split Slider](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/split-slider-wordpress-themes/)157
        * [Smooth Page Transitions](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/smooth-page-transitions-wordpress-themes/)77
        * [Intro Section Effects](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/intro-section-effects-wordpress-themes/)80
        * [Special Hovers](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/special-hovers-wordpress-themes/)81
        * [Special Effect Sliders](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/special-effect-sliders-wordpress-themes/)65
        * [Horizontal Scroll](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/horizontal-scroll-wordpress-themes/)62
        * [Special Cursors](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/special-cursors-wordpress-themes/)28
        * [Dynamic Background Color](https://qodeinteractive.com/theme-effect/dynamic-background-color-wordpress-themes/)9
* ###### Resources

Follow Us:

Privacy Policy
--------------

##### Qode Interactive

This Privacy Policy is brought by QODE LTD, incorporated and existing under the laws of Cyprus (hereinafter: QODE). QODE is the sole owner of a number of websites and platforms, including, but not limited to qodeinteractive.com, qodethemes.com, elated-themes.com, select-themes.com, edge-themes.com, mikado-themes.com, and a number of demo websites containing previews of WordPress website themes developed by QODE. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy the term “Platform” shall refer collectively to all websites and platforms owned by QODE and all their content, themes, codes, etc. This Privacy Policy shall apply to all QODE Platforms where this Privacy Policy is featured. This Privacy Policy describes how the QODE collects, uses, shares and secures personal information that you provide.

##### What kind of information do we collect?

To provide you with all information regarding our products and services, we must process certain information about you. The type of information we collect starts with you signing up for an account on the Platform, giving necessary information for opening of your account, such as your name, country of residence and email. We also collect the information regarding your IP address, log data and purchase code, as well as the information provided by cookies. You can learn how to access and delete information we collect upon request.

Things that you provide Information and content, you provide: We ask for and you provide us the necessary basic information about you when you sign up for an account on our Platform. The necessary data is requested in order to create your personal account that enables you to use all functionalities of the Platform, including but not limited to purchase of WordPress website themes (“Themes”) and ordering and obtaining of support services (“Services”). This information includes: your name and surname, country of residence, email address, as well as certain related information like your company name and website name, when you register for an account as legal entity. We refer to any information described above as ‘’Account Information’’ for the purpose of this Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Account Information, you represent that you are the owner of such personal information or otherwise have the requisite consent to provide it to us. Your Account Information is not publicly available and we do not publish on Platform any information provided by you, except the user name you have chosen when opening your account.

We may ask for and collect other personal information from you for other purposes such as: customer support, promotions, newsletter, collecting CVs and information contained therein on our career page. When submitting comments to the Platform you may also be required to provide some personal information (provided that you do not already have user account that you will use for commenting). Also, when you communicate with us directly (for example when we provide Support), we may ask for additional personal information if such information is necessary for performance of a particular task.

Please note that certain information (such as racial or ethnic origin, sexual orientation or philosophical beliefs) may be treated as sensitive data and could be subject to special protections under the laws of your country. Generally, we do not collect any sensitive data and in event that collection of such data is required you will be properly informed.

Log data and Cookies Like many operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Platform, further referred to as ‘’Log data’’. This Log data may include, among others, information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ‘’IP’’ address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Platform that you visit, the time and date that you visit, the time spent on those pages and information you search for. We connect personal information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve our Platform.

Our Platform also collects data from cookies stored on your device (including cookie IDs and settings) and the data obtained this way may differentiate depending whether you are logged in to your account. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are commonly used across the internet in order to make websites work, improve their personalisation, or to provide information to the owners of the site about how it is working. A cookie often contains a unique identifier, which can be used to recognise your computer when it returns to a website that it has visited before.

Pixels work with cookies to help us understand how you use our website and to improve our advertising, similar to cookies. Pixels are different from cookies because they do not stay on your computer, they are temporary while you browse our Site and are ‘removed’ when you close our Site.

Cookies are commonly classified into ‘first party’ and ‘third party’ cookies, and this changes whether we or one of our partners serves you the cookie. First party cookies are served by us and are more likely used to ensure performance of our Site, while third party cookies are hosted by one of our partners and more likely used for analytics and measurement of marketing performance.

Cookies may also have different lifetimes – this means that they stay on your computer for a defined period before being automatically removed. Another common cookie type is a ‘session cookie’, these cookies are automatically removed when you close your browser.

##### What information about you we receive from others?

In some situations, we need to obtain some information about you from third parties to whom you have provided certain information about yourself. This information is necessary for your uninterrupted use of the Platform’s functionalities.

When you use the Platform for purchase of the Themes and/or Services, we need to receive financial and/or transaction details from payment providers with whom you have made such payment. As we are the receiving party for such financial transaction, we need to have this information so we can be properly informed about the payment and provide you with purchased Themes and/or Services.

We also may receive information from other third-party sources, whereby we receive additional information about you (to the extent permitted by applicable law), such as fraud detection information, and combine it with information we have about you. Such data may be necessary to prevent frauds and secure safe and uninterrupted use of the Platform.

##### What kind of information may others collect when you are using the platform?

When using the Platform, you may be linked to third-party services that will collect certain personal information from you. This information is not collected or used by us and it is a subject to privacy policies of such third parties.

Payment Services When using the Platform for purchasing of Themes and/or Services, you will be redirected to third-party websites or platforms for completing the financial transaction. These websites and platforms will request certain information from you (including your credit card information) in order to carry out the payment. As we are the receiving party to this financial transaction, we will receive information about the transaction from third-party payment providers.

Embedded content The Platform may include embedded content (e.g. images, videos, articles, etc.) from third-party websites (such as YouTube, Vimeo, Google Web Fonts, SoundCloud, etc.). Accessing this embedded content makes the same effect as you are accessing third-party websites from which embedded content is provided. These third-party websites, therefore, may collect certain information about you in accordance with their own privacy policy. Please note that if you have an account on such third-party website and you are logged-in while accessing embedded content, such accessing will be attributed to your account. For example, interactions that you may make with embedded content will be traced by third-party website and the same may influence the user experience that you will have on such website.

##### How do we use the information that we collect?

We use the information to enable your use of the Platform and its features and to assure security of use and prevent any potential abuse. We may use the information that we collect for a variety of purposes including:

* Promotion — With your consent we send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about products and services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests and events;
* Promote safety and security — We use the information we have to verify accounts and activities, combat harmful conduct, detect and prevent spam and other bad experiences, maintain the integrity of the Platform, and promote safety and security. For example, we use data we have to investigate suspicious activity or violations of our terms or policies. When necessary we conduct the identity check of the users within the comment section in order to prevent the abuse of the comments and reviews.
* Verification of Services — We use the information we have in order to perform necessary checks and verifications regarding the use of support services. For example, we use purchase codes to verify whether you are entitled to use Services that you have gained by purchasing Theme via third-party website.
* Product research and development — We use the information we have to develop, test and improve our Platform and Services, by conducting surveys and research, and testing and troubleshooting new products and features.
* Communication with you — We use the information we have to send you various communications, communicate with you about our products, and let you know about our policies and terms. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us.

##### How is the information shared?

We do not share your personal information with third-parties unless it is necessary to carry out your request, for our professional or legitimate business needs, or as required or permitted by law.

Whenever we do transfer your personal information to third parties or services providers, appropriate arrangements are made in order to ensure correct and secure data processing in compliance with law.

We may share some collected information with our third–party service providers that we use to provide hosting for maintenance of our Platform, backup, storage, analytics, payment services and other services. These third-party service providers may have the access to or may process your personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or any other purpose not in connection with the services they provide to us.

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal information to the authorities, due to the court orders, legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, and we might share such an information in order to prevent any illegal activity, suspected fraud, or any type of violation of personal or other rights.

##### How can I manage or delete information about me?

If you wish to access or erase your data, you can contact us via [\[email protected\]](https://qodeinteractive.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) in order to give you the detailed instructions regarding this matter.

We store data until it is no longer necessary to provide our services within Platform, for example you Account will be active in order to provide you with our support, unless you request your account to be deleted. This is a case-by-case determination that depends on things like the nature of the data, why it is collected and processed, and relevant legal or operational retention needs. Your data related to the purchase record will be deleted upon each purchase or 2 years at latest.

When you delete your account, we may delete any content you have provided, and you will not be able to recover that information later.

##### How do we operate and transfer data as part of our Global Services?

We may share information globally, within QODE and our third-party service providers in accordance with this Policy. Your information may, for example, be transferred or transmitted to, or stored and processed in countries outside of where you live for the purposes as described in this policy. These data transfers may be necessary to provide the services set forth in Terms of Use of the Platform in order to provide our products and services to you. We utilize standard contract clauses, rely on the European Commission's adequacy decisions about certain countries, as applicable, and obtain your consent for these data transfers in accordance with applicable law.

##### How will we notify you of changes to this policy?

We'll notify you before we make changes to this policy and give you the opportunity to review the revised policy before you choose to continue using our Platform and related product and services.

##### How to contact us?

You can learn more about how privacy works within our Platform by contacting us. If you have questions about this Policy, you can contact us via below provided contacts. Additionally, we may also resolve any disputes you have with us in connection with our privacy policies and practices through direct contact.

QODE LTD  
[\[email protected\]](https://qodeinteractive.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

###### Company

###### Products

###### WordPress Themes

###### Magazine

###### Community

Powered by Qode Interactive 2024

##### Your Cart[](#)

Your cart is currently empty

Subtotal: ~$0~ $0.00

\*Taxes are calculated at the checkout

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However you may visit Cookie Settings to provide a controlled consent.

ACCEPTCookie settings

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_cfruid | session | Cloudflare sets this cookie to identify trusted web traffic. |
| AWSALBCORS | 7 days | This cookie is managed by Amazon Web Services and is used for load balancing. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-advertisement | 1 year | Set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin, this cookie is used to record the user consent for the cookies in the "Advertisement" category . |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| edd\_items\_in\_cart | 1 hour | This cookie is set by Easy Digital Downloads plugin.The cookie is used to store product cart information. |
| PHPSESSID | session | This cookie is native to PHP applications. The cookie is used to store and identify a users' unique session ID for the purpose of managing user session on the website. The cookie is a session cookies and is deleted when all the browser windows are closed. |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| G\_ENABLED\_IDPS | 7977 years 9 months 23 days 2 hours | Google uses this cookie for Google Single Sign-On. |

Performance

 performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_gat\_UA-139054615-2 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| AWSALB | 7 days | AWSALB is an application load balancer cookie set by Amazon Web Services to map the session to the target. |

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_ga | 2 years | The \_ga cookie, installed by Google Analytics, calculates visitor, session and campaign data and also keeps track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookie stores information anonymously and assigns a randomly generated number to recognize unique visitors. |
| \_gat\_UA-139054615-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gat\_UA-43336951-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gat\_UA-52920680-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gat\_UA-64910749-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gat\_UA-64911354-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gat\_UA-70731616-1 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gcl\_au | 3 months | Provided by Google Tag Manager to experiment advertisement efficiency of websites using their services. |
| \_gid | 1 day | Installed by Google Analytics, \_gid cookie stores information on how visitors use a website, while also creating an analytics report of the website's performance. Some of the data that are collected include the number of visitors, their source, and the pages they visit anonymously. |

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| fr  | 3 months | Facebook sets this cookie to show relevant advertisements to users by tracking user behaviour across the web, on sites that have Facebook pixel or Facebook social plugin. |

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| aso | 21 days | To allow website owners to track visitor behavior and measure site performance. |

Save & Accept

Log in

Don't have an account? [Sign up here.](#qodef-membership-register-modal-part)

 Remember me

Log in

Continue with your social network:

Sign up

Already have an account? [Log in here.](#qodef-membership-login-modal-part)

 Remember me

 Get the latest updates, news and discounts

Sign up

By clicking "Sign up", you agree to the [Terms of Use](https://qodeinteractive.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy Policy.](https://qodeinteractive.com/privacy-policy/)

Continue with your social network:

Reset Password

[Click here](#qodef-membership-login-modal-part) to return to Log in screen.

New Password

Continue with your social network:
